A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.3-SG 1.8 (A76-A82) FA209
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (A79), 1866-2003; 6; 101.47 Cubic Feet Box 383-651. 267 containers.; Document boxes 383-651.
  - Conflict in International Relations, 155; 5.55 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes and 1 half-legal document box
    - Conflict in International Relations - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Bowdoin College - Potholm, 1973-1976 (Box 435, Folder 2815-2816)
      - Bowdoin College - Potholm - Evaluation, 1975, 1977, 1979 (Box 435, Folder 2817)
      - Columbia University - Sen Gupta, 1974-1977 (Box 436, Folder 2818-2820)
      - Columbia University - Sen Gupta - Evaluation, 1974-1977 (Box 436, Folder 2821)
      - Columbia University - Sen Gupta - Supplementary Material, 1974-1976 (Box 436, Folder 2822-2824)
      - Coombs, Charles A., 1974-1975, 1980 (Box 437, Folder 2825-2826)
      - Coombs, Charles A. - Evaluation, 1975, 1977, 1979 (Box 437, Folder 2827)
      - Harvard University - Park, 1973-1978 (Box 437, Folder 2828)
      - Harvard University - Park - Evaluation, 1975, 1977, 1979 (Box 437, Folder 2829)
      - Harvard University - Park - Supplementary Material, 1972-1978 (Box 437, Folder 2830, Box 438, Folder 2831-2835)
      - Harvard University - Yergin, 1975-1976 (Box 438, Folder 2836)
      - Harvard University - Yergin, 1974-1976 (Box 439, Folder 2837)
      - Harvard University - Yergin - Evaluation, 1977, 1979 (Box 439, Folder 2838)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Pelcovitis, 1973-1977, 1979 (Box 439, Folder 2839-2842)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Pelcovitis - Evaluation, 1975, 1977, 1979 (Box 439, Folder 2843)
      - Middle East Institute - Fried, 1973-1975 (Box 440, Folder 2844-2845)
      - Middle East Institute - Fried - Evaluation, 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 440, Folder 2846)
      - Server, D., 1973-1977 (Box 440, Folder 2847)
      - Server, D. - Evaluation, 1977, 1979 (Box 440, Folder 2848)
      - Server, D. - Supplementary Material, 1974-1976 (Box 440, Folder 2849-2851, Box 441, Folder 2852-2855)
      - Southern Illinois University - Hsiao, 1974-1979 (Box 441, Folder 2856-2857)
      - Southern Illinois University - Hsiao - Evaluation, 1977, 1979, 1983-1984 (Box 441, Folder 2858)
      - Southern Illinois University - Hsiao - Supplementary Material, 1970, 1972-1974 (Box 441, Folder 2859)
      - Stanford University - Gould, 1974-1979 (Box 442, Folder 2860-2861)
      - Stanford University - Gould - Evaluation, 1977, 1979 (Box 442, Folder 2862)
      - Stanford University - Gould - Supplementary Material, 1968, 1970-1972 (Box 442, Folder 2863)
      - United Nations - Training and Research Institute - Epstein, 1971-1976 (Box 442, Folder 2864)
      - United Nations - Training and Research Institute - Epstein - Evaluation, 1977, 1979 (Box 442, Folder 2865)
      - United Nations - Training and Research Institute - Epstein - Supplementary Material, 1977 (Box 442, Folder 2866)
  - Education and Development in the Less-Developed Countries, 160; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Education and development in the less developed countries, 1973 (Box 443, Folder 2867)
  - 170, 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - 170: Illinois, 216
      - University of Chicago - Moawad, 1971-1976 (Box 443, Folder 2868)
  - United States, 200; 60 Cubic Feet 158 containers
    - Academic Affairs Conference of Midwestern Universities Minority Group Interns, 1972-1978 (Box 443, Folder 2869-2872)
    - Academic Affairs Conference of Midwestern Universities Minority Group Interns - Supplementary Material, 1973-1975 (Box 444, Folder 2873-2877, Box 445, Folder 2878-2879)
    - African-American Institute - Policy Information Center, 1971-1975, 1980 (Box 446, Folder 2880-2881)
    - American Indian Development Association, 1975 (Box 446, Folder 2882)
    - American Indian Development Association, 1974-1977 (Box 446, Folder 2883)
    - American Indian Development Association - Evaluation, 1977 (Box 446, Folder 2884)
    - American Indian Development Association - Supplementary Material, 1975-1978 (Box 446, Folder 2885)
    - American Indian Development Association - Supplementary Material, 1976 May 14 (Box 447, Folder 2886, Folder 2887)
    - American Institutes for Research - Desegregation conference, 1973-1976, 1980 (Box 447, Folder 2888)
    - American Institutes for Research - Desegregation conference, 1975-1976 (Box 447, Folder 2889)
    - American Institutes for Research - Desegregation conference - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 447, Folder 2890)
    - Atlanta - Education - Community Education, 1972-1977, 1980 (Box 447, Folder 2891)
    - Atlanta - Education - Community Education, 1968-1977 (Box 447, Folder 2892, Box 448, Folder 2893-2895)
    - Atlanta - Education - Community Education - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 448, Folder 2896)
    - Atlanta University Center Corporation, 1965-1975 (Box 448, Folder 2897-2898, Box 449, Folder 2899-2901)
    - Atlanta University Center Corporation - Supplementary Material, 1975, 1976 (Box 449, Folder 2902-2903, Box 450, Folder 2904)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Leadership Development, 1973-1975 (Box 450, Folder 2905)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Leadership Development - Supplementary Material, 1970-1974 (Box 450, Folder 2906-2908)
    - Brookings Institution - International Environment, 1974-1978 (Box 450, Folder 2909-2910)
    - Brookings Institution - International Environment - Book, 1978 (Box 450, Folder 2911)
    - Brookings Institution - International Environment - Evaluation, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 451, Folder 2912)
    - California Institute of Technology - Metal Pollutants, 1971-1976 (Box 451, Folder 2913-2915)
    - California Institute of Technology - Metal Pollutants - Supplementary Material, 1969-1971 (Box 451, Folder 2916-2917, Box 452, Folder 2918-2922, Box 453, Folder 2923-2925)
    - Case Western Reserve University - Environmental Systems Management, 1974-1977 (Box 453, Folder 2926-2927)
    - Case Western Reserve University - Environmental Systems Management - Evaluation, 1975-1979 (Box 454, Folder 2928)
    - Case Western Reserve University - Environmental Systems Management - Supplementary Material, 19741-1976 (Box 454, Folder 2929-2930)
    - Case Western Reserve University - Phosphorous Studies, 1971-1979 (Box 454, Folder 2931-2932)
    - Case Western Reserve University - Phosphorous Studies - Supplementary Material, 1971-1977 (Box 454, Folder 2933, Box 455, Folder 2934-2938, Box 456, Folder 2939-2944, Box 457, Folder 2945-2947)
    - Center for Information of America - Educational Materials, 1973-1979 (Box 457, Folder 2948-2950)
    - Center for Information of America - Educational Materials - Evaluation, 1976 (Box 457, Folder 2951)
    - Center for Information of America - Educational Materials - Supplementary Material, 1971-1977 (Box 458, Folder 2952-2953)
    - Citizens for Clean Air, Inc. - Energy Conservation, 1972-1977 (Box 458, Folder 2954)
    - Citizens for Clean Air, Inc. - Energy Conservation - Supplementary Material, 19731-1975 (Box 459, Folder 2958-2963, Box 460, Folder 2964-2966)
    - Citizens Commission on Science, Law and Food Supply - Food Additives, 1972-1976 (Box 460, Folder 2967-2970)
    - Citizens Commission on Science, Law and Food Supply - Food Additives - Supplementary Material, 1972-1974 (Box 461, Folder 2971-2972)
    - Claremont Colleges - Public Policy Studies, 1971-1977 (Box 461, Folder 2973)
    - Claremont Colleges - Public Policy Studies - Supplementary Material, 1971-1972 (Box 461, Folder 2974)
    - Coastal Plains Human Development - Coordinating Council, 1970-1975, 1982 (Box 461, Folder 2976, Box 462, Folder 2977-2978)
    - Coastal Plains Human Development - Coordinating Council - Evaluation, 1974-1975 (Box 462, Folder 2979)
    - Colorado State University - Mercury Content, 1971-1976 (Box 462, Folder 2980-2982)
    - Colorado State University - Mercury Content - Evaluation, 1974-1976 (Box 462, Folder 2983)
    - Cornell University - Environmental Perceptions Workshops, 1974-1976, 1979 (Box 462, Folder 2984)
    - Cornell University - Environmental Perceptions Workshops, 1973-1975 (Box 463, Folder 2985)
    - Cornell University - Environmental Perceptions Workshops - Supplementary Material, 1972-1975 (Box 463, Folder 2986-2988)
    - Cornell University - Pesticides, 1969-1976 (Box 464, Folder 2989-2990)
    - Cornell University - Pesticides - Supplementary Material, 1970-1972 (Box 464, Folder 2991)
    - Cornell University - Water Quality Management, 1974-1976 (Box 464, Folder 2992-2993)
    - Cornell University - Water Quality Management - Evaluation, 1976, 1980 (Box 464, Folder 2994)
    - Cornell University - Water Quality Management - Supplementary Material, 1975-1976 (Box 464, Folder 2995)
    - Council on Foundations, Inc. - Japanese Philanthropies, 1974-1975, 1979 (Box 464, Folder 2996-2997)
    - Duke University - Environmental Planning, 1973-1979 (Box 464, Folder 2998-2999)
    - Duke University - Environmental Planning - Evaluation, 1973-1974 (Box 464, Folder 3000)
    - Duke University - Environmental Planning - Supplementary Material, 1979 (Box 465, Folder 3001)
    - Equilibrium Fund - Center for Growth Alternatives, 1973-1979 (Box 465, Folder 3002-3003)
    - Fisk University - Development Program - Honors Program, 1971-1976 (Box 465, Folder 3004)
    - Fisk University - Development Program - Honors Program - Supplementary Material, 1965-1967, 1970 (Box 465, Folder 3005)
    - Franklin Institute Research Laboratories - Power Plant Aquaculture, 1972-1976, 1979 (Box 465, Folder 3006, Box 466, Folder 3007-3008)
    - Franklin Institute Research Laboratories - Power Plant Aquaculture - Supplementary Material, 1968, 1972, 1974 (Box 466, Folder 3009-3010)
    - Harvard University - Contraceptive uses of plants, 1974-1976, 1980 (Box 466, Folder 3011-3012)
    - Harvard University - Contraceptive uses of plants - Oversized Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 467, Folder 3013)
    - Harvard University - Land Use Planning, 1974-1976, 1979 (Box 468, Folder 3014-3015)
    - Harvard University - Land Use Planning - Supplementary Material, 1974 (Box 468, Folder 3016)
    - Harvard University - Medical Practice, 1959-1976 (Box 468, Folder 3017-3020)
    - Harvard University - Racial attitudes, 1968-1977 (Box 468, Folder 3021, Box 469, Folder 3022)
    - Harvard University - Racial attitudes - Evaluation, 1975-1977, 1979 (Box 469, Folder 3023)
    - Harvard University - Racial attitudes - Supplementary Material, 1971 (Box 469, Folder 3024)
    - Howard University - Leadership Development Institute, 1974-1977, 1980 (Box 469, Folder 3025-3026)
    - Howard University - Leadership Development Institute - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 469, Folder 3027)
    - Howard University - Leadership Development Institute - Supplementary Material, 1975 July-Dec. (Box 469, Folder 3028-3029)
    - Indiana State University - Backes, 1974-1975 (Box 469, Folder 3030-3031)
    - Indiana University - Law, Ethics and Biology, 1974-1976 (Box 470, Folder 3032)
    - Indiana University - Law, Ethics and Biology - Evaluation, 1974-1976 (Box 470, Folder 3033)
    - Iowa State University - Nitrogen Transformations, 1972-1977, 1980 (Box 470, Folder 3034)
    - Iowa State University - Nitrogen Transformations - Supplementary Material, 1968-1971 (Box 470, Folder 3035)
    - Kanawha County - Education - Community Schools, 1972-1977 (Box 470, Folder 3036-3038)
    - Kanawha County - Education - Community Schools - Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 470, Folder 3039)
    - Los Angeles - Education - Advisory Councils, 1971-1975 (Box 471, Folder 3040-3041)
    - Los Angeles - Education - Advisory Councils - Supplementary Material, 1971-1974 (Box 471, Folder 3042, Box 472, Folder 3043-3046)
    - Los Angeles - Education - Leadership Training, 1971-1976 (Box 472, Folder 3047-3048, Box 473, Folder 3049-3050)
    - Maine - Conservation - Public Land Management, 1974, 1976 (Box 473, Folder 3051)
    - Maine - Conservation - Public Land Management - Supplementary Material, 1974 Sept. (Box 473, Folder 3052, Folder 3053)
    - Massachusetts Audubon Society - Environmental Interns, 1973-1976, 1979 (Box 473, Folder 3054-3055, Box 474, Folder 3056-3058, Box 475, Folder 3059)
    - Massachusetts Vita, Inc. - Community Training, 1972-1974 (Box 475, Folder 3060)
    - Massachusetts Vita, Inc. - Community Training - Evaluation, 1975, 1981 (Box 475, Folder 3061)
    - Mercer University - Student Assistance, 1965-1967 (Box 475, Folder 3062-3063)
    - Mid-Hudson Patterns for Progress, Inc. - Hudson River Study, 1973-1977, 1979 (Box 475, Folder 3064-3065, Box 476, Folder 3066)
    - Mid-Hudson Patterns for Progress, Inc. - Hudson River Study - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 476, Folder 3067)
    - Mid-Hudson Patterns for Progress, Inc. - Hudson River Study - Supplementary Material, 1969-1975 (Box 476, Folder 3068-3071, Box 477, Folder 3072-3074)
    - Multi-Culture Institute - Regional Programs, 1973-1977 (Box 477, Folder 3075-3076)
    - Multi-Culture Institute - Regional Programs - Supplementary Material, 1974-1976 (Box 478, Folder 3077-3081)
    - National Academy of Sciences - International Foundation for Sciences, 1972-1975, 1979 (Box 478, Folder 3082)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People - Mississippi Litigation, 1976 (Box 479, Folder 3083-3084)
    - National Board of Young Men's Christian Association - Environment Control Conference, 1973-1976, 1979 (Box 479, Folder 3085-3088)
    - National Planning Association - Environment, 1973-1977 (Box 480, Folder 3089-3092)
    - National Planning Association - Environment - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 480, Folder 3093)
    - National Public Radio, Inc. - World Population Broadcast, 1974-1976 (Box 480, Folder 3094-3095)
    - New York Baptist City Society, 1955 (Box 481, Folder 3096)
    - New York Baptist City Society, 1972-1973 (Box 481, Folder 3097)
    - New York Ocean Science Laboratory - Marine Science, 1973-1977, 1979 (Box 481, Folder 3098-3099)
    - New York Ocean Science Laboratory - Marine Science - Supplementary Material, 1972-1975 (Box 481, Folder 3100-3102)
    - New York State Environmental Conservation Conference, 1970-1980 (Box 482, Folder 3103-3106)
    - New York University - Russell, 1972-1976, 1980 (Box 482, Folder 3107-3108)
    - New York University - Saunders, 1975-1976, 1978, 1980 (Box 482, Folder 3109-3110)
    - New York University - Saunders - Evaluation, 1976, 1979 (Box 482, Folder 3111)
    - Northwestern University - Insect Control, 1973-1975, 1979 (Box 482, Folder 3112-3113)
    - Northwestern University - Insect Control - Supplementary Material, 1971-1974 (Box 483, Folder 3114)
    - Oregon State University - Devine, 1976 (Box 483, Folder 3115)
    - Oregon State University - Devine - Evaluation, 1976-1980 (Box 483, Folder 3116-3117)
    - Oregon State University - Environmental analysis, 1974-1979 (Box 483, Folder 3118-3121, Box 484, Folder 3122-3123)
    - Oregon State University - Environmental Legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 484, Folder 3124)
    - Oregon State University - Environmental Legislation - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 484, Folder 3125)
    - Oregon State University - Rural Industries, 1973-1976, 1980 (Box 484, Folder 3126-3129)
    - Pathfinder Fund - Family Planning Manual, 1974-1976, 1979 (Box 484, Folder 3130, Box 485, Folder 3131)
    - Pathfinder Fund - Family Planning Manual - Supplementary Material, 1975-1976 (Box 485, Folder 3132)
    - Patterson Foundation - Catholic Church, 1975-1978 (Box 485, Folder 3133-3134)
    - Patterson Foundation - Catholic Church - Evaluation, 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 485, Folder 3135)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Environmental studies, 1969-1973 (Box 485, Folder 3136-3137, Box 486, Folder 3138-3142, Box 487, Folder 3143-3144)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Environmental studies - Supplementary Material, 1971-1972 (Box 487, Folder 3145-3148, Box 488, Folder 3149-3152)
    - Potomac Institute - Environment and Social Equity, 1975-1977, 1979 (Box 489, Folder 3153)
    - Potomac Institute - Environment and Social Equity - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 489, Folder 3154)
    - Potomac Institute - Environment and Social Equity - Supplementary Material, 1976 March (Box 489, Folder 3155)
    - Princeton University - Air Quality Sensors, 1971-1975 (Box 489, Folder 3156)
    - Princeton University - Air Quality Sensors - Supplementary Material, 1973 Oct. 18 (Box 489, Folder 3157)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc. - Urban Land Use and Public Transportation, 1973-1977 (Box 489, Folder 3158-3159)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc. - Urban Land Use and Public Transportation - Supplementary Material, 1973-1976 (Box 490, Folder 3160, Box 491, Folder 3161-3162)
    - Rocky Mountain Center on Environment - Water Quality, 1974-1976, 1979 (Box 491, Folder 3163-3164)
    - Sequatchie Valley Agency, 1969-1977 (Box 491, Folder 3165-3166, Box 492, Folder 3167)
    - Sequatchie Valley Agency - Supplementary Material, 1963, 1969-1972 (Box 492, Folder 3168-3171)
    - Siecus - Education Programs, 1973-1977, 1980 (Box 492, Folder 3172, Box 493, Folder 3173)
    - Siecus - Education Programs - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 493, Folder 3174)
    - Stanford University - Tribble, 1972-1976 (Box 493, Folder 3175-3176)
    - Stanford University - Tribble - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 493, Folder 3177)
    - Stanford University - Tucker, 1974-1980 (Box 493, Folder 3178-3180)
    - Stanford University - Turner, 1975-1976 (Box 494, Folder 3181)
    - Stanford University - Turner - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 494, Folder 3182)
    - Temple University - Urban Education, 1970-1975, 1980 (Box 494, Folder 3183-3184)
    - Trenton - Education - Leadership development, 1973-1976, 1980 (Box 494, Folder 3185)
    - United Nations National Commission for UNESCO - Educational Population Material, 1973-1976 (Box 494, Folder 3186)
    - United Nations National Commission for UNESCO - Educational Population Material - Evaluation, 1973-1975 (Box 494, Folder 3187)
    - United Nations National Commission for UNESCO - Educational Population Material - Supplementary Material, 1971, 1973-1975 (Box 494, Folder 3188-3189)
    - United Nations National Commission for UNESCO - Environmental Field Trips, 1973-1978 (Box 494, Folder 3190-3191)
    - United Nations National Commission for UNESCO - Environmental Field Trips - Evaluation, 1975, 1979-1980 (Box 494, Folder 3192)
    - United Nations National Commission for UNESCO - Environmental Field Trips - Supplementary Material, 1971, 1975 (Box 495, Folder 3193)
    - University of California - African Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 495, Folder 3194)
    - University of California - Environmental Programs Examination, 1974-1980 (Box 495, Folder 3195-3196)
    - University of California - Environmental Quality, 1969-1976 (Box 495, Folder 3197-3198)
    - University of California - Environmental Quality - Supplementary Material, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 495, Folder 3199)
    - University of California - Insect Control, Riverside, 1969-1976, 1979 (Box 495, Folder 3200, Box 496, Folder 3201-3202)
    - University of California - Insect Control, Riverside - Supplementary Material, 1972-1973 (Box 496, Folder 3203)
    - University of California - Pesticides, Berkeley, 1969-1976, 1979 (Box 496, Folder 3204-3206)
    - University of California - Pesticides, Berkeley - Supplementary Material, 1977 (Box 496, Folder 3207)
    - University of California - Pesticides, Riverside, 1969-1979 (Box 496, Folder 3208-3209)
    - University of California - Plant Resistance, Davis, 1970-1977, 1979 (Box 496, Folder 3210-3211)
    - University of California - Plant Resistance, Davis - Evaluation, 1976 (Box 497, Folder 3212)
    - University of California - Ward, 1972-1976, 1980 (Box 497, Folder 3213-3214)
    - University Corporation (for Atmospheric Research) - Sahelia Drought, 1974-1976, 1979, 1985 (Box 497, Folder 3215-3216)
    - University Corporation (for Atmospheric Research) - Sahelia Drought - Supplementary Material, 1974 (Box 497, Folder 3217)
    - University of Denver - International Studies, 1972-1976, 1980-1981 (Box 497, Folder 3218-3219)
    - University of Illinois - Pesticides, 1970-1977 (Box 497, Folder 3220-3222)
    - University of Illinois - Pesticides, 1972-1977 (Box 498, Folder 3223)
    - University of Illinois - Pesticides - Evaluation, 1976 (Box 498, Folder 3224)
    - University of Michigan - Douglas Lake Biological Station, 1972-1975, 1979 (Box 498, Folder 3225-3226)
    - University of Michigan - Douglas Lake Biological Station - Supplementary Material, 1972-1974 (Box 498, Folder 3227)
    - University of Michigan - Environmental Quality, 1969-1977 (Box 498, Folder 3228-3229, Box 499, Folder 3230-3232)
    - University of Michigan - Environmental Quality - Supplementary Material, 1971-1976 (Box 499, Folder 3233-3235, Box 500, Folder 3236)
    - University of Michigan - Systems Modeling (in Oahu), 1974-1977, 1979-1980, 1983 (Box 500, Folder 3237-3238)
    - University of Missouri - Environmental Trace Substances, 1971-1977 (Box 500, Folder 3239)
    - University of Missouri - Environmental Trace Substances - Supplementary Material, 1974-1976 (Box 500, Folder 3240-3241)
    - University of North Carolina - Water Management, 1972-1977 (Box 501, Folder 3242-3243)
    - University of North Carolina - Water Management - Supplementary Material, 1975-1976 (Box 501, Folder 3244, Box 502, Folder 3245)
    - University of Texas - Gill, 1975-1977 (Box 502, Folder 3246)
    - University of Texas - Gill - Evaluation, 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 502, Folder 3247)
    - Urban Institute - Ethnic Minorities, 1973-1978 (Box 502, Folder 3248, Box 503, Folder 3249)
    - Urban Institute - Ethnic Minorities - Supplementary Material, 1973-1974, 1978 (Box 503, Folder 3250-3251)
    - Urban League of Atlanta - Community Education, 1972-1975 (Box 503, Folder 3252)
    - Utah State University - Energy Futures, 1973-1976, 1979 (Box 503, Folder 3253-3254, Box 504, Box 3255-3256)
    - Utah State University - Land Use Planning Data Storage System, 1973-1976 (Box 504, Folder 3257)
    - Utah State University - Land Use Planning Data Storage System - Supplementary Material, 1971-1975 (Box 504, Folder 3258-3261, Box 505, Folder 3262)
    - Washington University - Environmental Dispute Mediation, 1973-1975, 1979 (Box 505, Folder 3263-3264)
    - Wayne State University - Jones, 1975-1977 (Box 505, Folder 3265-3266)
    - Wayne State University - Jones - Evaluation, 1975, 1979 (Box 505, Folder 3267)
    - Wilson, Woodrow, Foundation - Negro Veterans, 1968-1976 (Box 505, Folder 3268-3269, Box 506, Folder 3270-3271)
    - Wilson, Woodrow, Foundation - Negro Veterans - Evaluation, 1976 April-Aug. (Box 506, Folder 3272)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute - Water Pollution, 1973-1977, 1979 (Box 506, Folder 3273)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute - Water Pollution - Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 506, Folder 3274)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute - Water Pollution - Supplementary Material, 1974, 1976 (Box 506, Folder 3275)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, A
      - Albany Medical College - Family planning, 1972, 1974-1976, 1979 (Box 506, Folder 3276)
      - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, inc. - Abortion brochure, 1975-1976, 1979 (Box 506, Folder 3277)
      - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, inc. - Abortion brochure, 1975-1976 (Box 507, Folder 3278)
      - Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc., 1971-1977 (Box 507, Folder 3279-3280)
      - Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc. - Evaluation, 1976-1978 (Box 507, Folder 3281)
      - Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc. - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 507, Folder 3282)
      - Baylor College of Medicine - O'Malley, 1974-1977 (Box 507, Folder 3283)
      - Columbia University - Community health, 1971-1976 (Box 507, Folder 3284-3285)